exvo.com 2013-05-02

# Exvo - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy Disclaimer Terms & Conditions

  1. **Introduction**

Exvo.comâ€™s Privacy Policy applies to and covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Exvo.com anytime you interact with Exvo.com and its services, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Exvo.com products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. The scope of this privacy policy covers all of Exvo.com. It does not apply tot entities that Exvo.com does not own or control. By accessing or using Exvo.com and/or any related products/services you agree to our Privacy Policy.

Please take a moment to read the following privacy practices to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered through our services, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is very important to Exvo.com, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

  2. **Why is personal information collected?**

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer experience. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products, services and focus on categories of most interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

  3. **What information we collect and how we may use it**

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us provide you better products and improve our service standards. We collect for example the following personal information (not limitative).

    * When you sign up for your Exvo Account you provide us several items of personal information relevant to this situation, such as your name, gender, email address, phone number, contact preferences, IP address, credit card information, information about the Exvo product(s) you use/subscribe to, and information relating to a support or service issue.
    * To access some of the Exvo.com products/services, you will be asked to sign up/in with an email address and password, to which we refer as in this privacy policy as your â€˜Exvo Accountâ€™.
    * We may retain the details of transactions or banking and payment information about payments you make on Exvo.com (credit card information, account number).
    * Personal information when youâ€™re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading information, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, or purchasing a product.
    * We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve Exvo.comâ€™s products.
    * We gather information about your usage of, and interaction with the Exvo.com software products/services and websites including computer and connection information, device capability, bandwidth, traffic to and from our website and statistics on page views.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized Exvo.com experience, information collected through one of our products/services may be combined with other information obtained through other products/services you are using through Exvo.com.

  4. **How we may use your personal information**?

As mentioned before we primary collect your personal information to provide you a superior level of user experience when using our products/services. Exvo.com does collect and uses personal data related to you. This information we collect allows us to keep you informed about our latest products, news and so on.

    * By accessing Exvo.com and using a Exvo Account you agree to our mandatory service communications such as sending you, from time tot time, emails about information/technical service issues, any kind of important (technical) notices, billing reminders, security announcement, conditions, policies and more. Because of the high importance of this information, itâ€™s not possible to opt-out of receiving this kind of communications
    * By accessing Exvo.com and using a Exvo Account you allow us to send you promotional mailings about for example our latest product announcements, advertisements, marketing or promotional operations/offers, upcoming events, product surveys and more. If you donâ€™t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by changing your settings in your Exvo Account.
    * We also collect information for market research purposes to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service.
    * Your personal information may in certain situations be used to protect your and Exvo.comâ€™s interest, in particular to enforce our Terms & Conditions and to protect you against fraud.
    * We may use personal information to provide products/services that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve Exvo.comâ€™s products.
    * Your personal information collected by using Exvo.com products/services, may be stored and processed in any country in the world where Exvo.com or other service providers, related in any way to Exvo.com maintain facilities.
  5. **Your â€˜Exvo Accountâ€™ and related information**

The Exvo.com website, as well as Exvo.com services such as the Exvo Store, allows you to create an Exvo Account based on your personal information. This convenient service saves you time and allows for easier use of our web services.

This is how it works: You create a personal profile â€” providing your email address, and in some cases your name, phone number, mailing address and/or a credit card number â€” and choose a password. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal Exvo Account â€” in many cases simply your email address, because itâ€™s unique and easy to remember.

The next time you order from the Exvo Store or register for a new product, all you need to do is enter your Exvo Account and password; the system looks up the information it needs to assist you. In addition, if you update the information associated with your Exvo Account it will be available for all your transactions with Exvo.com globally.

Exvo.com also enables you to forward information to family members, friends or colleagues. To fulfill your request, Exvo.com may require personal information about the person to whom you are sending the product or service such as their name, physical address, email address, and so on. The personal information you provide about that person is used only for the purpose for which it is collected. Exvo.com will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

  6. **Disclosure of your personal information to third parties**

As mentioned before Exvo.com takes your privacy very seriously. Exvo.com does not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any personal information and/or traffic data to other marketers or any kind of third non-related parties without your explicit permission, except to the scenarios described below:

From time to time itâ€™s possible that we share your personal information and (traffic) data, if necessary, with other legal entities within the Exvo.com group to help us provide superior products/services. All those entities are committed to this Privacy Policy and will take steps to safeguard it. If necessary we also share your personal information and traffic data to companies where we have a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Exvo.com, in order to provide the best products/services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. Exvo.com will always require these third parties tot take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your personal information and (traffic) data and to observe the relevant legislation. Exvo.com cannot be held responsible in any way for the policies within the company of those third parties.

Exvo.com may offer products/services in connecting with other websites or services of (strategic) partners, or may team with any kind of other online services to deliver you the combined results of both products/services or any other additional benefits. In order to provide that kind of service we are entitled to share your personal information and/or (traffic) data.

Without such information as mentioned above being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products/services delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Exvo.com website.

At times we may be required by law, legal process, litigation and/or requests from public and governmental authorities throughout the world, to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, fraudulent activities or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary. Exvo.com will provide all reasonable assistance and information to fulfill this request and you hereby consent to such disclosure.

Exvo.com may disclose personal information and/or any data to enforce our policies, protect anyoneâ€™s rights, property and/or safety and to protect Exvo.comâ€™s interests. Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which Exvo.com, its group companies and/or other service providers maintain facilities. Exvo.com reserves the right to transfer any kind of data outside your country. By using Exvo.comâ€™s websites or Exvo.comâ€™s services/products you give us permission to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

We also may transfer personal information and/or data if we determine that itâ€™s necessary and reasonable to enforce our Terms & Conditions, or protect our products/services, our operations and/or users.

Exvo.com keeps continuing to develop its business. As we are doing so Exvo.com might buy or sell subsidiaries or business units, reorganize or restructure our organization. In such transactions or reorganizations/restructurings, personal information and data of exvo.com users will generally be transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information, collected as an asset, in such a transfer to a third party.

  7. **Protection of your personal information**

Exvo.com is very committed to protecting the security of your personal information and data. Exvo.com takes appropriate measures, including organizational, technical and physical measures, to protect your personal information and data provided or collected by it. We take these precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, misuse, destruction, as well as against unauthorized access and disclosure. We try to make sure that your personal information and data can only be accessed by authorized employees, consultants of Exvo.com or any other concerned Exvo.com group entities that need to have access to this information and/or data in order to be able to fulfill their duties.

The Exvo Store and Exvo.com applications use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Google Chrome, Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while itâ€™s transmitted over the Internet.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Keep your passwords confidential and change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser. Do not share this information with anyone. Be aware of the fact when sharing a (local) computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

Be aware that when you use some Exvo.com products, services or applications or the Exvo.com forum, the personal information you submit/share is visible to other users and it can be read, collected and/or be used by other individuals. Itâ€™s your own responsibility what kind of information you choose to submit in these instances. Please take care when using any kind of these features.

Exvo.com is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, Exvo.com will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

  8. **Information Integrity**

You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by checking them at www.exvo.com. You can request a copy of your personal information, your product registration history, and your interactions with our sales and support agents by contacting us at the email address below.

  9. **Third party products and linked websites**

Exvo.com websites may contain links that will let you leave Exvo.comâ€™s website in order to access another website. These linked website are not under control of Exvo.com and itâ€™s possible that these websites have a different privacy policy. This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information that is required on the Exvo.com websites or through the use of the any Exvo.com products/services. So Exvo.com encourages you to be careful when you enter personal information online. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for these other websites.

If you use/purchase any product of a third party within the Exvo Store of Exvo.com, the developer/provider of such applications may obtain access to certain personal information about you. However Exvo.com screens these products when they register as a precaution, however Exvo.com does not and cannot control how the provider of a product may use any personal information in connection with the use of that product. Please ensure that you review any privacy policies or other terms applicable to the use of such applications before using them.

  10. **Accessing your personal information**

Exvo.com has procedures in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. You always have the right to access and change or remove the personal information you have provided. In order to prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your credentials (email address and password) before your have access to your personal information.

If you want to stop using your Exvo Account you are able to deactivate or delete it. When you deactivate your account, no user will be able to see it. Your account will not be deleted. You still have the ability to reactivate your account. When you delete your account, it will be permanently deleted from Exvo.com. In this case we will use all reasonable endeavours to accommodate requests to delete personal information unless it is required to be retained by law or for lawful business purposes. We may decline requests that are unreasonable repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, are extremely impractical, jeopardize the privacy of others or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Please address any access, correction, or deletion requests to the email address below.

  11. **Cookies & other technologies**

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Exvo.comâ€™s website uses â€œcookiesâ€ to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalizing your online experience. A cookie can be described as a small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, or any other device. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences. These technologies help us to better understand user behavior, which parts of our websites are the most popular, where visitors are going and how much time they spent there and so on. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. By using cookies we can customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As user you have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most of the web browsers automatically accept cookies, but normally you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. Please take the note that if you decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Exvo.com. If you accept cookies you have the ability to later delete these cookies that you have accepted.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. This information and data is used by us to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about the user behavior on the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Exvo.com is entitled to use this information, which does not identify individual users, in our marketing and advertisement services.

In some of our email messages we use a â€œclick-through URLâ€ linked to content on the Exvo.com website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

  12. **Kids**

Exvo.com recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the Exvo.com purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to Exvo.com and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

  13. **Security**

In order to help secure your personal information and data, access to all this information on Exvo.com is password-protected as mentioned before. Sensitive data, such as credit card information is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and the Exvo.com website. To protect any personal information and data you store on our servers, Exvo.com regularly audits its system for possible attacks and vulnerabilities. Credit card data is stored by our Payment service provider to maximize security. Because the internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit through Exvo.com. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, changed, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information.

  14. **Commitment to your privacy**

As we said, Exvo.com takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to all Exvo.com employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

  15. **How long is your personal information kept by Exvo.com?**

Exvo.com will retain your information for as long as is necessary to fulfill any of the purposes as mentioned in this Privacy Policy and/or comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts. Exvo.com will not store your personal information and data as is necessary to fulfill our purposes or any other purposes as mentioned before.

  16. **Updates**

Exvo.com reserves the right to update the provisions of this Privacy Policy from time to time if deemed necessary. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be published on our website along with the updated privacy policy. Using any Exvo.com product/service after a notice of changes has been sent to you or published on our website shall constitute consent to the changed terms or practices. Thereby we advise you to regularly check out our website concerning this Privacy Policy.

  17. **Contact**

If you have any question or comments about this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@exvo.com or contact us at:

Exvo.com BV  
Weena 695 B07.044  
3013AM Rotterdam  
The Netherlands  
PO Box 259  
3000 AG Rotterdam  
The Netherlands
